[{"question": " y\u0092know what? it seems like all of the sudden; so much has happened.", "answer": " i know. ross is getting married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " phoebe is, making people.", "answer": " everybody\u0092s doing stuff!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " and we just sit here. i mean if i die the only way people would even know i was here, would be by the ass print on this chair! look, we have to do something. okay? something huge!", "answer": "  we could climb mt. everest!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " no-no, not something stupid, something huge.", "answer": " no-no-no-no-no, i saw an ad for this video, people climb that thing everyday! we could totally do that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " why not?! i mean it\u0092s just, it\u0092s just climbing! it\u0092s just, it\u0092s just steep!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " we\u0092re going to everest! okay, it would be nice to leave an ass print on everest!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " what-what\u0092s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " we\u0092re gonna climb mt. everest!", "answer": " yeah baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " really?! i looked into that. yeah, but, i mean it costs like $60,000 and y\u0092know you can die. and, you would die!", "answer": "  yeah, well\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " we could get that everest video though.", "answer": " yeah, we could do that without y\u0092know risking our lives at all!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " and while we\u0092re down at the video store, you know what else we could rent? die hard!  oh, y\u0092know what? i just remembered, that everest thing is only available through mail order.", "answer": "  oh, well\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " so you guys\u0092ll stay here and hang out with me?", "answer": " yeeeeahhhh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " yeah. yeah.", "answer": " but i\u0092ll tell you something. one of these days we\u0092re get off of our buts and rent die hard again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " so what did he decide? does your uncle nathan get an invite or not?", "answer": " ohh, god, nobody likes him, and he\u0092s so cheap, he\u0092d never fly to london in a million years. yeah, invite him? hey, did i do these neat enough?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " yeah, they\u0092re fine.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " if anyone asks, we\u0092ll just say ben addressed them.  oh! so you invited rachel then?", "answer": " sure. why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " i don\u0092t think i\u0092d be comfortable with any of my old lovers there.", "answer": " wait-wait-wait, do you, do you think, maybe we shouldn\u0092t invite her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh, no-no, y\u0092know i absolutely adore rachel it\u0092s just that, well it might be a awkward for you. but it\u0092s absolutely your decision.  more tea?", "answer": " yeah sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " earl grey?", "answer": " huh? yeah, fine, invite whoever you want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " rachel?!", "answer": " oh god monica hi! i just went to your building and you weren't there and then this guy with a big hammer said you might be here and you are, you are!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " okay, everybody, this is rachel, another lincoln high survivor.  this is everybody, this is chandler, and phoebe, and joey, and- you remember my brother ross?", "answer": " hi, sure!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " you know you probably didn't know this, but back in high school, i had a, um, major crush on you.", "answer": " i knew.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " you did! oh.... i always figured you just thought i was monica's geeky older brother.", "answer": " i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh. listen, do you think- and try not to let my intense vulnerability become any kind of a factor here- but do you think it would be okay if i asked you out? sometime? maybe?", "answer": " yeah, maybe...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " see, i see.... big passion in your future.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i do.", "answer": " oh ross, you're so great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " hey, i have a question. well, actually, it's not so much a question as.. more of a general wondering... ment.", "answer": " ok.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " ok. umm, for a while now, i've been wanting to, um....", "answer": " ohhh!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " yes, yes, that's right...", "answer": " oh, look at the little cat!  look at it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " what?  ow!", "answer": "  i'm on top of the world, looking down on creation and the only explanation i can find...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  yes! did you see that?", "answer": " you were incredible! brand new woman, ladies and gentlemen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " you had no right to tell me you ever had feelings for me.", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i was doing great with julie before i found out about you.", "answer": " hey, i was doin' great before i found out about you. you think it's easy for me to see you with julie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " alright, fine, you go ahead and you do that, alright ross.", "answer": " fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " 'cause i don't need your stupid ship.", "answer": " good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " ross do you realise this is the first time in my life i\u0092m doing something i actually care about. this is the first time in my life i\u0092m doing something that i\u0092m actually good at. i mean. if you don\u0092t get that...", "answer": " no, hey, i get that, okay, i get that big time. and i\u0092m happy for ya, but i\u0092m tired of having a relationship with your answering machine! okay, i don\u0092t know what to do anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " well neither do i!", "answer": " is this about mark?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  oh my god.", "answer": " okay, it\u0092s not, it\u0092s not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " oh my god. i cannot keep having this same fight over and over again, ross, no, you\u0092re, you\u0092re, you\u0092re making this too hard.", "answer": " oh i\u0092m, i\u0092m making this too hard. okay, what do you want me to do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, i don\u0092t know. urrrgh! look, maybe we should take a break.", "answer": " okay, okay, fine, you\u0092re right. let\u0092s ah, let\u0092s take a break,  let\u0092s cool off, okay, let\u0092s get some frozen yogart, or something..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " do i know why we\u0092re rushing?", "answer": " yeah, y'know the ah, the girlfriend i told you about last night?  well it turns out she ah, she wants to get back together with me. oh, i found it!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " that\u0092s so great for you guys!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " good luck, with your girlfriend.", "answer": " oh, thank you.  hey, hey.  rachel!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hi. ohhh, you got my message.", "answer": " yeah, oh hey, you are right on time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " so what do you say? can i be your girlfriend again?", "answer": " yes, you can, very much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  y'know what, i want you to leave! get outta here!", "answer": " no!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " just get out! now!!", "answer": " no!! no!! i wanna stay. i wanna talk about this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " was she good?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " come on ross! you said you wanted to talk about it, let\u0092s talk about it!! how was she?", "answer": " she was...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " awful! horrible!", "answer": " she was not good. not good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " ewwwww!", "answer": " uh-oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " good different?", "answer": " nobody likes change.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " ...the way you owned up to everything, it just showed me how much you\u0092ve grown. y'know? i mean my mom never thought this would work out. it was all, \u0093once a cheater, always a cheater.\u0094 ooh, i just wish we hadn\u0092t lost those four months, but if time was what you needed just to gain a little perspective...", "answer": " we were on a break!!!!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " you seem to really like her.", "answer": " yeah, i really do. yeah, but what am i gonna do, i mean we-we both agreed that it was gonna be a two-week thing, y\u0092know no commitment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " ross, that girl just spent the entire evening talking to your friends, asking to hear stories about you, looking through monica\u0092s photo albums, i mean you don\u0092t do that if you\u0092re just in it for two weeks.", "answer": " you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yeah, you got like 14 hours until she has to be at the airport, and you\u0092re sitting here in the hallway with a 28-year-old cheerleader with a fat lip.", "answer": " hey, you\u0092re right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " ohh, this is soo amazing! i can\u0092t believe my brother\u0092s getting married! and in london! it\u0092s so romantic!", "answer": "  hey, pretty smart! tissue paper! you\u0092re at the wedding, you have to cry, \"handkerchief?\" \"no-no, i got my invitation.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oooh look! isn\u0092t this adorable, ross let ben address mine!", "answer": "  hello!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hey! hey, did you get your invitation to ross\u0092s wedding?", "answer": "  noo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " don\u0092t worry man, i get to bring a guest. we\u0092ll show him.", "answer": " i\u0092m so jealous you\u0092re all going! i can\u0092t believe i never knew that you can\u0092t fly in your third trimester!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i didn\u0092t know that.", "answer": " i never knew that either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " i knew that!  i sooo didn\u0092t know that, but you should see your faces.", "answer": "  hey guys! what\u0092s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " what\u0092s this? is this ross\u0092s wedding invitation?", "answer": " see, maybe that\u0092s the one we should\u0092ve actually hidden.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " oh, no! no you guys! come on, you don\u0092t have to do that! i\u0092m happy for him! i am! i really\u0097i\u0092m-i\u0092m happ\u0097i\u0092ll work on it.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry honey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " rach, you\u0092re gonna come though aren\u0092t you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh, honey, i don\u0092t know. i\u009a", "answer": " this isn\u0092t one of those uh, y\u0092know \"if she doesn\u0092t come, we-we don\u0092t, we don\u0092t come?\" right? because i already bought my ticket\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " you know what would be real weird? is if you weren\u0092t there. just say you\u0092ll think about it, okay?", "answer": " no, i\u0092ll think about it. yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " who's this from?", "answer": " oh, that's ross's.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh... ...  oh my god. he remembered.", "answer": " remembered what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " it was like months ago. we were walking by this antique store, and i saw this pin in the window, and i told him that it was just like one my grandmother had when i was a little girl. oh! i can't believe he remembered!", "answer": " oh, it's so pretty. this must have cost him a fortune.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i can't believe he did this.", "answer": " come on, ross? remember back in college, when he fell in love with carol and bought her that ridiculously expensive crystal duck?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " what did you just say?", "answer": "  f-hah.... flennin....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " well, ross and i were in grad school together.", "answer": " but we haven't seen each other since then. well i land in china, guess who's in charge of the dig.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " oh, that is so sweet. no, no, ok, you hang up. ok, ok, one, two, three. well you didn't hang up either.", "answer": " she didn't hang up either...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " you're over me?", "answer": " ohhhhhhhh god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " wha... you're uh, you're, you're over me?", "answer": " ohh, ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " when, when were you... under me?", "answer": " well, basically, lately, i've uh, i've uh, sort of had feelings for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " he broke up with julie. well, go hug her, for god's sakes.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " really. it's always been you, rach.", "answer": " oh, god.  chandler and joey: ohhh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " i've no idea, could be. listen, i'm sorry i had to work tonight.", "answer": " oh it's ok. you were worth the wait, and i don't just mean tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " ah, oh god. oh, honey, oh that's ok.", "answer": " what. oh no, you just rolled over the juice box.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " gunther! gunther. gunther, please tell me you didn\u0092t say anything to rachel about me and the girl from the xerox place.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry. was i not supposed to?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " y'know, hey! you\u0092re the one who ended it, remember?", "answer": " yeah, because i was mad at you, not because i stopped loving you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " you still love me?", "answer": " noo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " what does this mean? what do you, i mean do you wanna, get back together?", "answer": " noo! maybe! i, i don\u0092t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " i just, i feel, i-i just...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " y'know i can\u0092t believe i even thought about getting back together again! we are so over!!", "answer": "  fine by me!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " and hey! just so you know, it\u0092s not that common! it doesn\u0092t happen to every guy! and it is a big deal!!", "answer": " i knew it!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh my god.", "answer": " you know what this is, this is us getting ready for the prom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " you know what, you guys, we don't have to watch this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " oh yeah we do. c'mon.", "answer": " get a shot of monica. where's monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " wait, how do you zoom out?  there she is.", "answer": " shut up, the camera adds ten pounds.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " oh, dad, turn it off.", "answer": " it is off. right ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " i can't go to my own prom without a date, i can't, it's too late.", "answer": " if you're not going then i don't want to go either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " y'know what? i think we've seen enough, let's turn it off.", "answer": " no, no, no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " ok, fine, well i'm not gonna watch, alright.", "answer": " c'mon kid, let's go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " ahh, are you hadsome.", "answer": " let's show 'em.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": "  ok dad.", "answer": "  rachel, ready or not, here comes your knight in shining... no.  rachel, monica, roy, and chip: bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " oh, dear. jack, how do i turn this off?", "answer": " i can't believe you did that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": "  nooooo. you\u0092re really not going?", "answer": " yeah. it\u0092s just gonna be too hard. y\u0092know? i mean, it\u0092s ross. how can i watch him get married? y\u0092know it\u0092s just, it\u0092s for the best, y\u0092know it is, it\u0092s\u009a y\u0092know, plus, somebody\u0092s got to stay here with phoebe! y\u0092know she\u0092s gonna be pretty big by then, and she needs someone to help her tie her shoes; drive her to the hospital in case she goes into labour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " you don\u0092t have a car. and your license expired.", "answer": " i know.  yeah, see, there\u0092s so much to do and i have so little time to do it in. closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " all right, check it out. check this out. it says here that there\u0092s a place you can go to rent videos of all the museums!  \"it\u0092s almost as good as being there.\"", "answer": " it\u0092s better! you can\u0092t go to a museum in your underwear!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " well, you could, but... probably just the one time.", "answer": " i bet we could get videos of all the sites, get a vcr in our hotel room... we'd never even have to go outside!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " if we do that, we gotta get die hard.", "answer": " oh-ho! i bet the british version is gooooood!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}]